John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, Corporate Structure, RG 1 FA1793
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Incorporation Papers, 1950-2015; 2; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Other, 1990-2015; 4; 0.1 Cubic Feet
    - Internal Revenue Service Determination, Grant-making Procedures, 2014 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      IRS determination letter re: educational grant procedures. The IRS granted approval for procedures for awarding KF educational grants and has determined that any expenditures made under those procedures are not taxable. Original letter with legend defined and one without (which will be publicly disclosed).
    - California Franchise Tax Board, 2014 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      Exempt Acknowledgement Letter from the State of California acknowledging KF's federal tax exempt status as a 501(c)(3) private foundation since 4/1/1995. Therefore, California tax-exempt status is effective from the same date.
- Organizational Charts, 1995-2002; 3; 0.19 Cubic Feet 1 half-letter box
  These folders contain organizational charts with information about the reporting structure of staff of the Knight Foundation from 1995-1997. Also includes "Family Tree" pictorial organization charts of trustees and staff, 2002-2014.
  - Organizational Chart, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Organizational chart of staff positions (no names), 5/4/95.
  - Organizational Chart, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Organizational chart of staff positions (no names), proposed March 1996.
  - Organizational Chart, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Organizational chart of staff positions (no names), July 1997.
  - "Family Tree" Visual Organization Chart, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Organizational charts of staff and trustees, with pictures, names and positions.